

SUMMARY

I am a full stack web developer. The main technology stack is Angular + NodeJS. I have 4 years of personal experience and 2 years of commercial experience in web development. I had a little experience as a team lead and with Agile methodology.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Birth date

23.05.2001

Location

Saint-Petersburg

CONTACT

- npozdeyev@gmail.com
- +7-931-243-51-11
- https://pniklta.github.io /Portfolio-Website/
- https://www.linkedin.com /in/nikita-pozdeyev-570949203/
- https://github.com/PNiklta

Pozdeyev Nikita

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full stack developer

INSPIRATION POINT

August 2023 - to the current time

Making a website for live watching competitions results. Making frontend side on Angular and backend side on NestJS. Using websockets for live refreshing data and docker for deployment. Using elastic stack for logging and grafana for colleciing metrics.

Front end developer

INVIGLOB COMPANY

March 2023 - April 2023

Freelance order. Making admin panel for inviglob company website using React (NextJS framework) and deployment to the server.

Front end developer

NAVULLIA October 2022 - May 2023

Startup project. Making front end side on Angular. Here was my first experience of using Agile methodology.

Content-Manager

N-LINK COMPANY

September 2021 - March 2022

Filling content on website. Making web pages according to mockups.

EDUCATION

UX analytics and designing information systems

HIGH SCHOOL OF ECONOMYCS

2023 - to the current time

Programming

STEP IT ACADEMY

2019-2021

Computer Engineer

NATIONAL AVIATION ACADEMY

2018-2022

LANGUAGES

Russian - native speaker English - B2 Azerbaijani - B1

SKILLS (FRONT-END)

Angular HTML/CSS/SCSS React

SKILLS (BACK-END)

NodeJS (NestJS framework) MSSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Elastic Search Kibana stack

Grafana C# (ASP.NET Core, WPF)

SKILLS (DEVOPS AND OTHER)

Git Docker Figma Agile Methodology Design Patterns Linux administration